(Raj:)Maybe you don't want
(Raj:)someone exactly like you.
You know what they say:
opposites attract.
(Sheldon:)Well, by that logic,
(Sheldon:)I should be with someone short,
dull and needy, eh?
(Sheldon:)Not to cast aspersions,
(Sheldon:)but I can't shake a stick around
here without hitting that.
(Dave:)You know, I once
drove 500 miles
(Dave:)to hear him speak
at Stanford.
(Amy:)I have a DVD of that lecture.
(Dave:)Really? Wasn't it great?
(Amy:)Not as a Valentine's
present, no.
(Dave:)Well, the next time
you watch it,
(Dave:)I'm the bloke who
asked the question
(Dave:)that he said was
stupid and obvious.
(Dave:)It was the nicest thing
he said to anyone there.
(Amy:)That's, um, terrific.
Listen, I'm-I'm kind of tired.
Can we call it a night?
(Dave:)Oh, gosh. Sorry,
I've just spent the whole night
(Dave:)talking about your ex-boyfriend.
(Dave:)I'm such an idiot.
(Amy:)No, you're not.
(Dave:)Well, maybe not an idiot,
but certainly not as smart as...
(Dave:)someone we won't mention.